<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</title>
    <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.prestashop-project.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/code-of-conduct/code-de-conduite-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/code-of-conduct/code-de-conduite-fr/</guid>
      <description>Charte Code de Conduite PrestaShop v1.0 Version française.
Notre engagement Dans l&amp;rsquo;intérêt de favoriser un environnement ouvert et accueillant, nous nous engageons, en tant que responsables et en tant que personnes contribuant à ce projet, à faire de la participation une expérience exempte de harcèlement pour tout le monde, quel que soit le niveau d&amp;rsquo;expérience, le sexe, l&amp;rsquo;identité ou l&amp;rsquo;expression de genre, l&amp;rsquo;orientation sexuelle, le handicap, l&amp;rsquo;apparence personnelle, la taille physique, l&amp;rsquo;origine ethnique, l&amp;rsquo;âge, la religion ou la nationalité.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/modules-themes/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/modules-themes/readme/</guid>
      <description>List of third party, open source and free of charge modules and themes for the PrestaShop e-commerce solution There are plenty of useful themes and modules available on the web from third party developers for the PrestaShop e-commerce solution. Unfortunately, there is no place currently to list them so people can find them.
So, let&amp;rsquo;s build a knowledge base. If you want to contribute to this page, please create a pull request for each module or theme you would like to propose, following the example:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/slack/apps-and-integrationsapps-and-integrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/slack/apps-and-integrationsapps-and-integrations/</guid>
      <description>List of apps and integrations used in Slack Productboard  Description: Productboard is a product management tool, used by the PrestaShop Core&amp;rsquo;s product team to gather feedback, organize and prioritize features and improvements to build, and to follow their development. These feedback are grouped together to create &amp;ldquo;features ideas&amp;rdquo; that you can see at http://feedback.prestashop.com/. The Productboard app connects this Slack to the PrestaShop&amp;rsquo;s Productboard.
It allows the product managers to transform a Slack message (and its comments) into a feedback &amp;ldquo;note&amp;rdquo; on productboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/slack/channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/slack/channels/</guid>
      <description>Slack channels A Slack dedicated to the PrestaShop open source project is now available. Its purpose is to foster the development of the software and of its ecosystem. The current priority is to configure channels for development and product management purpose. Once done, it will be open more progressively to other needs, like community management, business, etc.
More information about prestashop.slack.com
Request a new channel Creating a new channel is reserved to the administrators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the PrestaShop Project</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/about/</guid>
      <description>What is PrestaShop? PrestaShop is an open-source e-Commerce content management system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
