<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maintainer&#39;s guide on PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</title>
    <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maintainer&#39;s guide on PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project organization</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/project-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/project-organization/</guid>
      <description>Project organization Project roles Product Managers Product Managers provide the product vision for the project, ensuring that the software meets the needs of its various users.
Current product managers:
 Fabien Vallon (@fabienvallon) Mateus Shirlaw (@MatShir)  Project Maintainers Project maintainers provide the technical vision for the whole project, reviewing and merging code contributions, while ensuring that the software is developed according to the product vision.
Current maintainers:
 Franck Lefèvre (@Progi1984) Ibrahima Sow (@sowbiba) Jonathan Lelièvre (@jolelievre) Krystian Podemski (@kpodemski) Mathieu Ferment (@matks) Matthieu Rolland (@matthieu-rolland) Pablo Borowicz (@eternoendless) Pululu Kinanga André (@PululuK) Thomas Baccelli (@atomiix) Valentin Szczupak (@NeOMakinG)  Scoped Maintainers Scoped Maintainers have the same mission as Project Maintainers, but over a limited scope (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to become a maintainer</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/how-to-become-a-maintainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/how-to-become-a-maintainer/</guid>
      <description>How to become a maintainer In the PrestaShop project, maintainers are contributors with merge rights.
The maintainer status is a position of great power, but it also carries great responsibility. As gatekeepers to the project&amp;rsquo;s code, maintainers are ultimately responsible for every contribution that is included in the project.
Candidates can apply to become maintainer over the whole project, or just a scope (a project, a repository, or a technology).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary of how GitHub Issues and Pull Requests are processed</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/summary-github-lifecycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/summary-github-lifecycle/</guid>
      <description>Summary of how GitHub Issues and Pull Requests are processed GitHub is the main tool used by maintainers to manage the PrestaShop project.
This page quickly describes how Issues and Pull Requests are processed on GitHub.
The teams On GitHub, there are mainly three teams working together on the project.
 Product Team: this team takes care of the product vision of the software. It has Product Managers, UX Designers and Wording Managers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing and approving Pull Requests</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/reviewing-pull-requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/reviewing-pull-requests/</guid>
      <description>.content label { display: inline; border-radius: 2em; font-size: 80%; font-weight: bold; color: #000; padding: .3em .8em; white-space: nowrap} label[type=needs] { background-color: #FBCA00; } label[type=check] { background-color: #B9EC4F; } label[type=branch] { background-color: #6270E9; } label[type=type] { background-color: #D4C5F9; } label[type=category] {} label[type=bcbreak] { background-color: #FF7854; } label[type=keyfeature] { background-color: #FFB33A; } label[type=needsdoc] { background-color: #D93E0B; color: #fff; } label[type=wip] { background-color: #FF8800; } label[type=e2e] { background-color: #EDEDED; } label[type=migration] { background-color: #00E031; }  Reviewing and approving Pull Requests All contributions to the PrestaShop project are subject to review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release a native PrestaShop module</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/release-a-native-ps-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/release-a-native-ps-module/</guid>
      <description>Release a new version of a native PrestaShop module Some modules are embedded within PrestaShop ZIP archives and loaded through Composer package manager. They consequently are listed in the composer.json of the Core project.
This is what we call &amp;ldquo;native PrestaShop modules&amp;rdquo;. The source code of these modules is hosted on GitHub.
This page explains what is needed to release these modules.
Requirements Mandatory requirements The module should be valid which means:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License &amp; license compatibility</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/license/</guid>
      <description>License &amp;amp; license compatibility In order to protect PrestaShop users from patent trolls, it&amp;rsquo;s important to make sure that all content included and distributed with PrestaShop is covered under homogeneous license terms.
The PrestaShop Core software is released under the OSL 3.0 license. Therefore, all original work included in PrestaShop itself must be released under that license as well.
PrestaShop&amp;rsquo;s Native Modules and the Classic theme are released under the AFL 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Processes</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/</guid>
      <description>Processes Security recommendations Maintainer GitHub accounts are granted extended rights on the PrestaShop organization.
We require from maintainers to take the necessary steps to make sure this account is protected. This means, but not only:
 enable 2FA on GitHub use a safe and strong password be very careful about GitHub tokens granting account accesses  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
