<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How to release on PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</title>
    <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How to release on PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to release a native module</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/native-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/native-module/</guid>
      <description>Release a new version of a native PrestaShop module Some modules are embedded within PrestaShop ZIP archives and loaded through Composer package manager. They consequently are listed in the composer.json of the Core project.
This is what we call &amp;ldquo;native PrestaShop modules&amp;rdquo;. The source code of these modules is hosted on GitHub.
This page explains what is needed to release these modules.
Requirements Mandatory requirements The module should be valid which means:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to release a new AutoUpgrade version</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/autoupgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/autoupgrade/</guid>
      <description>Release a new version of AutoUpgrade module The AutoUpgrade module is released following the same process as the native modules.
However, after the release has been published, a last step is necessary.
Mark the new version as latest The AutoUpgrade module is able to detect whether a new version is available. If it detects a new version is available it will suggest to user to upgrade itself to the new higher version.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
