<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</title>
    <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bug Bounty</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/bug-bounty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/bug-bounty/</guid>
      <description>Bug bounty A bug bounty for security flaws is hosted on YesWeHack platform.
The program is currently paused. Please report security issues to security-core@prestashop.com instead. This email address allows to report security issues of the PrestaShop project, but it is not part of a bug bounty program. Visit the Bug Bounty page
This bounty program covers code from the GitHub repository PrestaShop/PrestaShop and all PrestaShop modules defined in the composer.json file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security policy</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/security-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/security-policy/</guid>
      <description>Security Policy Obviously, PrestaShop project security is a critical matter. Project members are dedicated to keeping a high level of security in every aspect of the software.
However a software without vulnerability does not exist, which is why there is a security report process. If you find a security issue, please follow it to responsibly disclose your findings.
Reporting a Vulnerability Security issues can be reported by sending an email to security-core@prestashop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security release process</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/security-release-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/security-release-process/</guid>
      <description>Security release process Here is a short summary of the steps followed by the security team:
  Security issues are reported to security-core@prestashop.com or through the Bug Bounty Program.
  Security issues are assessed to identify their criticality level.
   Minor issues are scoped to be fixed in the next scheduled minor release Critical issues are scoped to be fixed as soon as possible   For both minor and critical issues, a GitHub Security Advisory will be created to register the issue in GitHub&amp;rsquo;s CVE database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing third-party distributions</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/sharing-third-party-distributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/security/sharing-third-party-distributions/</guid>
      <description>Sharing third-party distributions For user safety, please do not link to or reference forks or third-party repositories of PrestaShop releases or PrestaShop distributions that are not officially maintained by the PrestaShop project team. This applies to all parts of the project, including comments, issues, pull requests, discussions, Build Blog, and Slack.
Such links may be removed or hidden by the maintainers. Repeated promotion may result in further moderation.
Only repositories under the official PrestaShop or PrestaShopCorp GitHub organizations, as well as the official prestashop.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
