<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How to release a new PrestaShop version on PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</title>
    <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How to release a new PrestaShop version on PrestaShop Project - Open Source e-Commerce platform</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preliminary tasks</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/preliminary-tasks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/preliminary-tasks/</guid>
      <description>Preliminary tasks Before you can start your build, you must make sure that the project is ready to be built.
1. Create the new version in Addons Marketplace and update native module compatibility This step requires special rights (doc to create a new version on Addons).
Ask a maintainer from the PrestaShop Company with administrative rights on the Addons Marketplace to perform this step.
 This only needs to be done once per release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security patch releases</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/security/</guid>
      <description>Security patch releases Context In the past, we used to mix security fixes for major security issues and regular Pull Requests, but that made releasing new versions of PrestaShop harder. Today when there is a major security vulnerability reported, we fix it in a scoped security patch release which contains only the security fixes.
Examples: PrestaShop 8.1.6 or PrestaShop 8.1.4
For regular patch releases, we start from the content of the patch branch to create a new build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create the build</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/create-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/create-build/</guid>
      <description>Create a build package Once preliminary tasks have been completed, the project is ready to be built.
1. Communicate Starting this step means that the Development phase of this release is over.
Before you go further, make sure to tick the &amp;ldquo;Development&amp;rdquo; box in the Release Tracker GitHub issue (there is one per version, see the 1.7.6.6 example).
2. Create a local branch for your build The following tasks will require you to perform changes and submit them as a Pull Request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release publicly</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/release-publicly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/release-publicly/</guid>
      <description>Release the version publicly Once the QA team has greenlighted your build, you can move forward with the public release.
Make certain you have go for publish! Also, avoid starting this process after 4 PM or on a Friday. 1. Merge security PRs on GitHub If there are unmerged security PRs:
 Merge them on GitHub and publishing their security advisories. Rebase the build branch that you created on the previous step to remove the merge commits from the security PRs you merged manually before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final steps</title>
      <link>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/final-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.prestashop-project.org/maintainers-guide/processes/release/prestashop/final-steps/</guid>
      <description>Final steps 1. Update API stream for 1-click upgrade This should only be done for stable releases.
(i.e. if not for betas and RCs).
 This step requires special rights.
Ask a maintainer from the PrestaShop Company with administrative rights on the PrestaShop API repository to perform this step.
 Here is an example of a PR that introduces a new version https://stash.prestashop.com/projects/PA/repos/xml/pull-requests/138/diff:
 you will need to add the new XML checksum file that was generated with the zip archive, this XML file should be named after the version released (ex: for 8.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
